{
    "subject": "resource/Jos\u00e9_Domingues_dos_Santos",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Santos",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos is Santos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878118634223938,
            "question": "What is the surname of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9628626704216003,
            "question": "How would you refer to Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos by his surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9617894291877747,
            "question": "If someone wanted to find Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos, what surname should they look for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.961237907409668,
            "question": "What is the last name of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9601338505744934,
            "question": "What name comes after 'dos' in the full name of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9487086534500122,
            "question": "What is the family name associated with Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9185962677001953,
            "question": "Which name is used as a family identifier for Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.889563262462616,
            "question": "If you were introducing Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos to someone, what last name would you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7505196928977966,
            "question": "Who is known as Santos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.739886462688446,
            "question": "How do we identify the branch of the family that Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos belongs to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos is Santos.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2055_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known as Santos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2055_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were introducing Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos to someone, what last name would you use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2055_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which name is used as a family identifier for Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2055_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2055_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context provided does mention that Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos had the surname \"Domingues\" and that \"dos Santos\" was the surname of his husband, indicating that \"Santos\" can be part of the surname in some cases. Therefore, the statement that the surname of Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos is Santos is supported by the information given."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states that Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' surname is \"Santos,\" but the text clearly says his surname was \"Domingues dos Santos.\"",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' surname was not mentioned as being Santos, but rather as being the surname of his husband, Jose dos Santos.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Jos\u00e9 Domingues dos Santos' full name includes \"dos Santos,\" indicating that \"Santos\" is a part of his surname, not just his last name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}